haircolorforwomen.com 2016-11-07

# eSalon - Privacy Policy

**Last updated: May 1, 2015**

### Data and Information Overview

This privacy statement is for the website www.eSalon.com ("Site") operated by eSalon.com, a Delaware limited liability company ("eSalon", "we" or "our"). Visitors to the website and our users may be called "you" or "your" in this Statement. We respect your privacy and endeavor to comply with all applicable privacy laws where our users are located. eSalon collects personal and other information from you in order to enable you to purchase hair colour and hair care products on the Site that may be customized to meet your hair needs. eSalon will not sell, share, or rent any information to any third party, except as indicated in this privacy statement. The information that we collect (unless we indicate that we don't store it) is stored on our dedicated servers, whether located at eSalon or at a secure offsite facility. 

### Information We Collect and How It Is Used

We collect information about you so that you can order and purchase our hair products on our Site, and to enhance your shopping experience. Such information may include your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and your credit card and other payment information ("personal information" or "personal data"). We also collect information relating to your personal appearance, hair characteristics, and hair-dyeing habits from our clients in order to formulate custom hair care products. We may also collect data we gather from your use of the Site, the pages you visit and the options you select, as well as the IP address you use to access the Site. Much of this data, called analytics, is collected in the aggregate in anonymized fashion to optimize the operation of the Site and improve the user experience. We also may use personal information/data to prevent fraudulent transactions, and to communicate with you about any promotions, news about products or services, or notices that may be of interest, subject to applicable law including anti-spam laws.

You will be given the opportunity to establish an online account, and to create your unique login password, and change such password as you desire. In order to protect your account and your personal information, you should not share your login information with anyone. We also do not share this information with third parties. 

### When Your Information Is Shared

eSalon will use the services of third parties for certain purposes. These purposes may include credit card processing, order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, and data analysis. The third parties we contract with for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes or transfer it.

eSalon does not store your credit card information. In order to process credit card payments, eSalon uses the service of secure payment processors/gateways such as Authorize.Net, and the credit card information you provide goes directly to such a processor (where it is subject to their privacy policy) and is encrypted and transmitted via such gateways to financial institutions for authorization and approval. For your own protection and ours, we may also use the fraud screening services of third party companies. When your data or information is in the possession of such third parties/sites, your data and information are subject to such third party privacy policies, not this Privacy Statement. 

eSalon does not sell, rent or transfer your personal information, except as otherwise indicated herein.

eSalon may also share your personal information/data as necessary to comply with court orders, legal process, judicial or arbitral proceedings and as requested by government agencies or as necessary to protect our rights and public safety.

In connection with any sale of eSalon or any line of business (including the assets relating thereto), client information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and such client information (including your personal information) will be transferred or sold to the acquirer in the event of any such sale or disposition, and your use of the Site constitutes your consent to such transfer.

We will not display your personal information on the Site unless you choose to display it. If you post any content on the Site (such as comments or other text, testimonials, photos or videos), you can associate any "display name" you choose with your content or activity, as long as it is available. We recommend that you choose a user name that protects your own privacy online.

### Partnerships and External Sources

The Site may include links to external sites. eSalon is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or external websites. eSalon recommends that you use commercially reasonable judgment and prudence when navigating to other websites, and that you review the privacy policies of the sites you visit when you leave our Site, as eSalon shall not be liable for any damages or harm suffered while visiting or using an external website. This privacy statement covers only the way eSalon treats the information it collects on its own Site. 

In some cases our Site may frame, mask or include components of third party websites or content within our interface where it may appear that you have not left our Site. In such cases, eSalon will review the privacy practices of such sites, and will include such components or webpages only after determining that such sites maintain a comparable commitment to privacy as eSalon.

### Cookies

Cookies are bits of text or identifiers that enable a website to "remember" you, either for the duration of your visit, a "session cookie," or for repeat visits (a "persistent cookie"). Cookies enable you to navigate between pages efficiently, storing your preferences, remembering what is in your shopping cart, and generally enhancing your shopping experience by making your visit faster and easier. If we did not put cookies on your hard drive through your browser, you would appear to be as new visitor each time you came to the Site, and you would not remain logged in if you have an account. Moreover, because we use cookies, if you return to the Site to reorder products, you may not have to answer questions that you answered on prior visits (e.g., your preferred shipping address). The Help function on the toolbar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of eSalon's most important features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, each shopping experience on the Site may feel like the first time you made a purchase on the Site and entered all of the information we required. 

There may be cookies on our Site placed by other websites who run content on the page you are visiting ("third party cookies") and we have no access or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by eSalon only ("first party cookies") and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

### Security

eSalon uses commercially reasonable efforts and mechanisms to protect the security of your personal information. In order to assure you that the webpages where you provide personal information are trustworthy and secure, such transmission of information will be encrypted and the webpages where such information is collected, such as your account pages, will be SSL certified by a reputable Internet certification organization such as GeoTrust. Nonetheless, you provide your personal information at your own risk. We try to store your personal information securely until such time as it is no longer required or has no further use, as set forth in applicable law. We encourage you to communicate with us should you wish to know what personal information we store about you, or should any of your personal information need modification, or in the event that you wish it to be removed, at privacy @esalon.com. 

### Notices

At the time of your order, you may opt-in to receive optional notifications from eSalon. Optional notices are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive them. You may also log into your account and indicate that you no longer wish to receive optional notices.

### Changes and Notifications

We reserve the right to make modifications to this Privacy Statement. Changes would become effective 48 hours from the time the modifications are announced on the Site. If we make material changes to this Statement, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. In addition, please check the "Last updated" date at the top of this Statement, which will indicate when the last changes have been made to this Statement. Your continued use of the Site after such modifications are announced on the Site constitutes your acceptance of such modifications.

### Governing Law

eSalon is based in California, and our servers are also US-based. By accessing or using the Site, or any of eSalon’s services, or by purchasing products on the Site, you agree that your use of our Site is governed by the laws applicable in the State of California, and you expressly consent to the processing of personal information/data in, and transfer of your personal information/data to, the United States (and any other countries where eSalon may in the future hold such data, subject to the security representations set forth in this Statement). While we accept orders from outside of the United States, and we treat your personal information with great care, we do not purport to comply with all applicable laws in all other jurisdictions where our users may be located.

### Contact Us

eSalon.com, LLC  
Attention: Privacy c/o Legal Dept.  
10361 Jefferson Blvd  
Culver City, CA 90232  
privacy@esalon.com
